(tools rattling)
(sparks buzzing)
(upbeat music)
♪ I throw my hands up
in the air sometimes ♪
♪ Say ayo, gotta let go ♪
♪ I wanna celebrate and live my life ♪
♪ Saying ayo, baby, let's go ♪
♪ I came to dance, dance, dance, dance ♪
♪ I hit the floor ♪
♪ 'Cause that's my plans,
plans, plans, plans ♪
♪ I'm wearing all my favorite
brands, brands, brands, brands ♪
♪ Give me some space ♪
♪ For both my hands, hands, hands, hands ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 'Cause it goes on and on and on ♪
♪ And it goes on and on and on ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I throw my hands up
in the air sometimes ♪
♪ Saying ayo, gotta let go ♪
♪ I wanna celebrate and live my life ♪
♪ Saying ayo, baby, let's go ♪
♪ 'Cause we gon rock this club ♪
♪ We gon go all night ♪
♪ We gon light it up like it's dynamite ♪
♪ 'Cause I told you once,
now I told you twice ♪
♪ We gon light it up like it's dynamite ♪
♪ I came to move, move, move, move ♪
♪ Get out the way of me and
my crew, crew, crew, crew ♪
♪ I'm in the club so I'm
gonna do, do, do, do ♪
♪ Just what the (censored)
came here to do, do, do, do ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 'Cause it goes on and on and on ♪
♪ And it goes on and on and on ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I throw my hands up
in the air sometimes ♪
♪ Saying ayo, gotta let go ♪
♪ I wanna celebrate and live my life ♪
♪ Saying ayo, baby, let's go ♪
♪ 'Cause we gon rock this club ♪
♪ We gon go all night ♪
♪ We gon light it up ♪
♪ Like it's dynamite ♪
♪ 'Cause I told you once ♪
♪ Now I told you twice ♪
♪ We gon light it up like it's dynamite ♪
♪ I'm gonna take it all ♪
♪ I'm gonna be the last one standing ♪
♪ Higher over all ♪
♪ I'm gonna be the last one landing ♪
♪ 'Cause I, I, I believe it ♪
♪ And I, I, I, I just want it all ♪
♪ I just want it all ♪
♪ I'm gonna put my hands in the air ♪
♪ Hands in the air ♪
♪ Put your hands in the air ♪
♪ I throw my hands up
in the air sometimes ♪
♪ Saying ayo, gotta let go ♪
♪ I wanna celebrate and live my life ♪
♪ Saying ayo, baby, let's go ♪
♪ 'Cause we gon rock this club ♪
♪ We gon go all night ♪
♪ We gon light it up ♪
♪ Like it's dynamite ♪
♪ 'Cause I told you once ♪
♪ Now I told you twice ♪
♪ We gon light it up ♪
♪ Like it's dynamite ♪
(crowd cheering)